usersdrive.com 2019-06-06

# UsersDrive.com - Easy way to share your files

At UsersDrive.com we care about the privacy of your data and are committed to protecting it. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect about you and why, what we do with that information, and how we handle that information. Throughout this policy, when we write "UsersDrive" or "we" or "us," we're referring to UsersDrive., a Delaware corporation, and our subsidiaries and other affiliates.: 

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") is incorporated into UsersDrive's Terms of Service and License Agreement located at UsersDrive.com/tos.html (the [Terms Of Service](https://usersdrive.com/tos.html)") and applies to the information obtained by us through your use of UsersDrive's Site, and Services (Information") as described in this Policy. Capitalized terms used in this Policy and not otherwise defined shall have the meanings provided for those terms in the Terms of Service. 

Information collection and use  
**What Information does UsersDrive collect about me?** When you interact with our Site, and/or Services, we collect Information that, alone or in combination with other data, could be used to identify you ("Personal Data"). Some of the Information we collect is stored in a manner that cannot be linked back to you ("Non-Personal Data").  
**Information you provide us when you create an account**   
When you signup for or use our Services, you voluntarily give us certain Personal Data, including:

 **Automatically collected Information**  
Certain data about the devices you use to connect with UsersDrive and your use of the Site and/or Services are automatically logged in our systems, including:

 **How does UsersDrive use my Information ?**  
We use, process, and store your Information as necessary to perform our contract with you and for our legitimate business interests, including:
